babylontraffic.com 2019-05-14

# Privacy Policy - Babylon Traffic

## 1\. Introduction

Kevin Lion - Y4321331J  
Calle Parroco Francisco Rodriguez Rodriguez 44  
35010 Las Palmas de Gran Canaria  
Spain 

The above-referred is the owner and operator of this web site (“We/Us” or “Babylon Traffic”), and he is committed to your privacy, as data controller. This Privacy Policy details how we use your personal identifying information and just by navigating this web site, you are accepting its terms. This Privacy Policy may be modified at any time without notice to you. 

Please review this document each time you visit us or use any of our tools or services. 

## 2\. General Information

You can access our Website home page without disclosing your personal data, but some aspects of our site are available to registered members only and as our terms require, you must provide us with the required registration information, which has to be complete, accurate and up to date. 

The purposes of the processing of your personal data is to provide you information of our services and, eventually, hiring them by you, including a demo subscription. These data will be basic ones, such us your e-mail those needed for payments (complete name, card number, etc.). If you do not provide the data requested, you may not access to the function seeked. The legal basis for the processing is your own consent, which you can withdraw at any time, without affecting the lawfulness of the processing until then. 

The only recipients of your personal data are the controller and the eventual processors that he hire just in order to fulfill the service that we provide to you regarding the purposes of the processing described above. 

Please, note that the processing of your data may mean an international transfer if you are located in a third country of the European Union. 

Your personal data will be stored by the controller just for the strictly necessary time to fulfill the purposes of the processing, or more of required by law. You also have the right to request from the controller access to and rectification or erasure of personal data or restriction of processing concerning the data subject or to object to processing as well as the right to data portability. However, you may lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority (In Spain, you can contact the Agencia Española de Protección de Datos - AEPD) 

## 3\. Cookies

Please note that we may employ the use of cookies. Such usage of cookies could be when users create user accounts, but we may further employ cookies to assist the functionality of other tools, services and functions in the future. 

Cookies are small programs that enhance your use of the Internet, in general, and specifically we use cookies to enhance your usage of our functions. The cookies that we use are the functionality ones and our own. 

You can, however, disable cookies via your website browser settings. This may mean, however, that you may no longer have access to some of our website features. Please note that even with all cookies disabled, a tiny amount of information will continue to be retrieved from your web browser. This information is necessary for the basic functioning of our website. 

In order to seek out and repair functionality issues with our servers and related programming, we may use your email and IP addresses for evaluation and diagnostic purposes. 

Cookies may provide Recording Session information, show us visitor preferences regarding return visits to our website, help us to mange subscription or private areas on our website or record user specific tracking. None of the information gathered is shared with third parties. 

Other possible uses for the information that we collect include internal tracking, review, or is used for contacting purposes and then is archived by us for future usage. 

## 4\. Further Information

We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measure to protect the personal data that we have under our control. These policies, rules and technical measures help to protect your data from unauthorized access, improper use or disclosure, unauthorized modification, and unlawful destruction or accidental loss. However, note that no policy, rule or technical measure can offer 100% protection against unauthorized access, improper use or disclosure, unauthorized modification, unlawful destruction or accidental loss. 

All our data processors, who have access to, and are associated with the processing of personal data, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of our visitor's and user's personal data. 

Please [contact us](https://www.babylontraffic.com/contact) if you should have any questions, comments or concerns about this privacy policy.
